const data =[
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others.',
        options: ['A. arriv','B. believ','C. receiv','D. hop'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'D. hop',
        note:' To join hands = work together : Cùng nhau, chung sức, cùng làm việc '

    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. open','B. knock','C. play','D.occur'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'B. knock',
        note:'Take the responsibility for +V_ing : nhận trách nhiệm     Ex: You have to take the responsibility for watching out your child'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others.afsafas',
        options: ['A. rubb','B. tugg','C. stopp','D. fill'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'C. stopp',
        note:'be in a hurry : vội vã'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. dimm','B. travell','C. pass','D. stirr'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'C. pass',
        note:'Night shift : ca đêm'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. tipp','B. begg','C. quarrell','D. carri'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'A. tipp',
        note:'close-knit (a) quan hệ khăng khít  - a very close-knit family'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. tri','B. obey','C. clean','D. ask'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'D. ask',
        note:'close-knit (a) quan hệ khăng khít  - a very close-knit family'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. pack','B. add','C. clean','D. pronounc'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'B. add',
        note:'close-knit (a) quan hệ khăng khít  - a very close-knit family'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. watch','B. phon','C. referr','D. follow'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'A. watch',
        note:'close-knit (a) quan hệ khăng khít  - a very close-knit family'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. agre','B. succeed','C. smil','D. lov'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'B. succeed',
        note:'close-knit (a) quan hệ khăng khít  - a very close-knit family'
    },
    {
        question:'EXERCISE 1: Choose the word whose underlined part is pronounced differently from the others',
        options: ['A. laugh','B. wash','C. help','D. weigh'],
        options1: 'ed',
        correct_option:'D. weigh',
        note:'close-knit (a) quan hệ khăng khít  - a very close-knit family'
    },
]
export default data;
